phoolwala.com 2017-04-04

# Phoolwala.com Privacy Policy to Send Flowers Gifts to India| Phoolwala.com

Phoolwala.com gathers personal information to help improve our products and customer support, to communicate with our customers, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and more personalized shopping experience and to inform you, and your gift and message recipients, of special offers and discounts from us. We recognize and respect the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers, registered members and users, and have established this Privacy Policy as a result. 

**1\. How do we handle my contact information which I enter during the purchasing process?**

All customers’ contact information, choice of bouquets, and delivery date entered at the Delivery Information Form during the purchasing process are stored in our secured merchant server database. All the printouts for record purpose are securely kept. 

2\. **For what purpose will my contact information be used?**

Customer's contact information will be used for the following purposes:   
a. Market Analysis Such information as customer's choice of flowers/gifts, country of the senders and the recipients, are used to identify markets that need our services. The information and the result of analysis are solely meant for internal use and will be kept confidentially.  
b. Channel for Communicating Purchase and Delivery Status Sender's email will be used as a channel for communicating purchase status (e.g. confirmation of purchase by forwarding the receipt to the customer) and delivery status (e.g. update customer if the order has been fulfilled).   
c. Products Update Sender and recipient's email addresses will be used for forwarding new products updates.  
d. Festival and Other Promotions: Sender and recipient's email addresses will be used for Festival and Other Promotions. 

3\. **Do we collect and store my credit card information?**

No. We do not collect and store your credit card information. We do not get any idea of Credit Card number. During the purchasing process, you will enter your credit card information directly into the form posted by the credit card payment gateway. Hence, all your credit card information will be collected and secured by the credit card payment gateway directly in most secured way.

**Corrections**

If you would like to update or correct information previously provided to us, please send an e-mail with your new information, including your complete name, postal address, and email address to admin@phoolwala.com.  
Registered users can modify and update their membership information (including name, mailing address, telephone number and email address) by accessing the password-protected "Edit Profile" page.

**Your Consent and Changes to this Policy  
**  
Subject to the above provisions, by using our Web Site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use, of which this policy is a part. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time as new features are added, suggestions from our customers are incorporated or other changes are made. We will post the revised Privacy Policy on our Web Site at least 30 days prior to their effective date - unless we believe changes must take effect sooner to comply with law or to protect the Company or our customers, users, Members, recipients, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants, Associates and Affiliates, in which case the changes will be effective upon posting or as otherwise specified.

**Your Comments**

Phoolwala.com welcomes feedback concerning this Privacy Policy. Please send your comments and questions to 

[admin@phoolwala.com](mailto:admin@phoolwala.com%22 "admin@phoolwala.com").

**Marketing Policy**

1\. **Who does Phoolwala.com send email offers to?**

Phoolwala.com sends email offers to individuals who would require their services for sending gifts to India.

2\. **How does Phoolwala.com get email addresses for it's email offers?**

Phoolwala.com, as a web marketer, procures opt-in email lists from partner sites. Users have an option to opt for receiving newsletter and offer mail while registering on Phoolwala.com. 

3\. **How often does Phoolwala.com send emails to people on the email lists?**

Phoolwala.com generally sends emails announcing special gifts for festive seasons, promotional discounts and new arrivals once a month. However, the recipient always has the option of removing their email address from our list. Information on how to do this is always contained at the bottom of every email offer. If the recipient chooses this option, they will not get further email offers from Phoolwala.com. 

4\. **Can Phoolwala.com affiliates send email offers on behalf of Phoolwala.com?**

Phoolwala.com affiliates can send emails on behalf of Phoolwala.com only to people who have opted-in to receive such email offers. If an affiliate is found to be sending unsolicited email, their affiliation is revoked immediately. 

5\. **How do I Opt out from receiving promotional communication?**

If you want Opt out from Phoolwala.com’s newsletter list, you can simply reply to the mail with UNSUBSCRIBE in its subject. 

6\. **What can I do if I find unsolicited mail from a Phoolwala.com affiliate?**

We encourage you to contact immediately to our Customer Support. Please give us as much details as you can.
